TRUONG NGUYEN QUANG KHUONG

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



- **** +84987049314
- ☑ khuongtnq@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/khuongtnq
- khuongtnq.azurewebsites.net

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Seeking a position to apply the knowledge that I have learned and explore abilities, skills, towards my duties and to excel in field of Java. I hope to have the opportunity onsite in future.

HOBBIES

- * Read book
- * Traveling and photography
- * Exercise (hiking, swimming).
- * Participate in social activities

EXTRA ACTIVITIES

- * Join the ACM / ICPC National Contest programming contest.
- * The 12th Green Summer Volunteer Campaign of VNU-HCM Information Technology University

SUMMARY

A software engineer worked more than 1 year. I am responsible for writing well designed, testable, and efficient code using specific software to create web pages. I must stay plugged into emerging technologies and trends to ensure that the website is current and well maintained at all times.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Major: Computer Science

Research models for knowledge representation and design knowledge bases. Besides that, develop automated reasoning method to apply in the practical intelligent systems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2019 CITYNOW COMPANY

BOOKS PROJECT

My roles: Java Back-End Developer + Sub Leader

Programming language: Spingboot Restfull, SpringSecurity, Neo4j, React JS, Redux.

My achievements:

- Collaborated with frontend engineers to see projects through, from conception to completion.
- Contributed creative ideas and insight for improving usability of our web tools.
- Using database connection using JPA, understanding MVC architecture in Springboot.
- Using AWS to send mail, save photos, deploy projects. Team working and communicate with Japanese customers on Telegram and Wantedly to communicate.
- Using Backlog to manage tasks and Gitlab to manage codes in the project.
- Deploying / Hosting Spring Boot applications on AWS EC2 using Ubuntu Server for back-end and using S3 for font-end.

2018 - 2019 CITYNOW COMPANY

CROWDFUNDING PROJECT

My roles: Java Back-End Developer + Sub Leader

Programming language: Spingboot WebFlux, SpringSecurity, Mongo DB, React JS, Redux, Next JS.

My achievements:

- Using Spring 5 has embraced reactive programming paradigm by introducing a brand new reactive framework called Spring Webflux.
- Using MongoDB as our data store along with the reactive mongodb driver. All the REST APIs will be asynchronous and will return a Publisher.
- Integrated user-facing elements developed by front-end developers with server side logic.
- Estimated effort for architecture, logic, and development tasks.
- Designed new features and services to support client applications.
- Using AWS to send mail, save photos, deploy projects. Team working and communicate with Japanese customers on Telegram and Wantedly to communicate.
- Using Backlog to manage tasks and Gitlab to manage codes in the project.
- Deploying / Hosting Spring Boot applications back-end and font-end on AWS
 EC2 using Ubuntu Server for testing.

SKILLS



Databases

Neo4j graph database, Mongo DB, MySQL, Postgre SQL



Languages

Java Programming, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, JavaScript



Applications

Web Development Tools & IDE: Intellji, NetBean, Visual Code, SublimeText, GitLap, GitHup,...

Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint



Server/Systems

Amazon Web Services EC2, PC/Server, Routers, MacOS, Ubuntu



English Skill Reading and Writing